{
    "cards" : [
        {
            "front" : "diamond",
            "back" : "el diamante"
        },
        {
         "front" : "to approach",
         "back" : "acercar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "ghost",
            "back" : "espíritu"
        },
        {
            "front" : "uncomfotable",
            "back" : "incomodo"
        },
        {
            "front" : "well (as in 'well, laney')",
            "back" : "pues"
        },
        {
            "front" : "compliment",
            "back" : "el piropo"
        },
        {
            "front" : "courtesy",
            "back" : "cortesía"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to treat/try",
            "back" : "tratar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "abruptly",
            "back" : "abruptamente"
        },
        {
            "front" : "ground",
            "back" : "el suelo"
        },
        {
            "front" : "nightmare",
            "back" : "pesadilla"
        },
        {
            "front" : "arm",
            "back" : "el brazo"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to vomit",
            "back" : "vomitar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to jump",
            "back" : "saltar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to hit",
            "back" : "pegar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "nose",
            "back" : "la nariz"
        },
        {
            "front" : "horridly",
            "back" : "horrorizada"
        },
        {
            "front" : "yahoo",
            "back" : "uaju"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to grab",
            "back" : "agarrar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "mysteriously",
            "back" : "misteriosamente"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to wink",
            "back" : "guiñar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "snob",
            "back" : "el esnob"
        },
        {
            "front" : "advice",
            "back" : "el consejo"
        },
        {
            "front" : "interest",
            "back" : "el interés"
        },
        {
            "front" : "palm tree",
            "back" : "la palmera"
        },
        {
            "front" : "view (like a scene)",
            "back" : "la vista"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to explain",
            "back" : "explicar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "so",
            "back" : "así"
        },
        {
            "front" : "then",
            "back" : "luego"
        },
        {
            "front" : "at last",
            "back" : "por fin"
        },{
            "front" : "nevertheless",
            "back" : "sin embargo"
        },{
            "front" : "tower",
            "back" : "la torre"
        },
        {
            "front" : "sound",
            "back" : "el sonido"
        },
        {
            "front" : "half asleep",
            "back" : "media dormida"
        },
        {
            "front" : "it is",
            "back" : "sea"
        },
        {
            "front" : "tower",
            "back" : "la torre"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to leave",
            "back" : "dejar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "upon",
            "back" : "al"
        },
        {
            "front" : "line",
            "back" : "la fila"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to sit",
            "back" : "sentar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "soft",
            "back" : "suave"
        },
        {
            "front" : "a lot",
            "back" : "muchísmo"
        },
        {
            "front" : "over there",
            "back" : "por allí"
        },
        {
            "front" : "enthusiasm",
            "back" : "entusimaso"
        },
        {
            "front" : "spontaneous",
            "back" : "espontánea"
        },
        {
            "front" : "adventurous",
            "back" : "aventurera"
        },
        {
            "front" : "in fornt of",
            "back" : "frente"
        },
        {
            "front" : "ice cream shop",
            "back" : "la heladería"
        },
        {
            "front" : "glass",
            "back" : "el cristal"
        },
        {
            "front" : "image",
            "back" : "la imagen"
        },
        {
            "front" : "ridiculous",
            "back" : "ridículo"
        },
        {
            "front" : "shameful",
            "back" : "avergonzada"
        },
        {
            "front" : "team",
            "back" : "el equipo"
        },
        {
            "front" : "camp",
            "back" : "el campamento"
        },
        {
            "front" : "altough",
            "back" : "aunque"
        },
        {
            "front" : "dumb",
            "back" : "tonto"
        },
        {
            "front" : "anxiously",
            "back" : "ansiosamente"
        },
        {
            "front" : "neither",
            "back" : "ni"
        },
        {
            "front" : "how",
            "back" : "podria"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to escape",
            "back" : "escapar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to surprise",
            "back" : "sorprendir"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to mention",
            "back" : "mencionar"
        },
        {
            "front" : "proud",
            "back" : "orgulloso"
        },
        {
            "front" : "great uncle",
            "back" : "tío abuelo"
        },
        {
            "front" : "the rest",
            "back" : "el resto"
        },
        {
            "front" : "I realized that...",
            "back" : "dio cuenta de"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to get dirty",
            "back" : "ensuciarse"
        },
        {
            "front" : "sticky",
            "back" : "pegajoso"
        },
        {
            "front" : "tower",
            "back" : "la torre"
        },
        {
            "front" : "to attend",
            "back" : "asistir"
        }
    ]
}
